

Inês Moreira Informatics Engineer

Summary

Software developer with 2+ experience in frontend development. I've built responsive applications in React, Angular 4+ and collaborated also in AngularJS applications.

I am an organized person, watchful to details and have a critical and analytical thinking.

I also have a 4-year experience as an architect, but I decided to change my route and started a new career in Information Technologies in September 2016.

Professional experience

04/2021 - 12/2022

Software developer | Connectlime, Lisbon

- Migrate an AngularJS app to Angular 11, using Angular Material components;
- Add features to AngularJS applications;
- Implement UI for mobile and web applications (responsive) in React, Bootstrap and Material UI libraries;
- Build reusable code and UI components;
- Translate user needs into functional frontend code;

09/2020 - 02/2021

Software developer | Visionspace Technologies GmbH, Darmstadt

- Design and implement UI solutions for building a cybersecurity knowledge graph;
- Analysis of the impact of cyber threat information and its attack patterns, actors;
- Build reusable code and UI components, using Angular and Clarity Design library

11/2015 - 07/2016

Architect | Interdesign Interiores, Porto

01/2014 - 30/2015

Architect | Sousa Lima & Rocha Reis, Porto

05/2012 - 02/2013

Intern architect | Orange - Arquitectura e Gestão de Projecto Lda, Coimbra

Education

09/2016 - 06/2020

Bachelor's degree in Informatics Engineering | University of Coimbra

09/2004 - 09/2011

Masters in Architecture | University of Coimbra

10/2009 - 09/2010

Erasmus | Rheinische - Westfälische Technische Hochschule Aachen

Personal info

Phone

916166169

Email

inesvanbrabant@gmail.com

Skype

ines van brabant

GitHub

github.com/inesvbm

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/inês-moreira-

339515203

Languages

Portuguese - native

English - advanced (C1)

Spanish – advanced (C1)

French – intermediate (B1)

Technical skills

React

Angular 4+ | AngularJS

JavaScript

Typescript

Redux | NgRx

HTML

CSS

Java

_

PostgreSQL

MySQL

GIT

Jira

Bootstrap

Material UI

Angular Material

Clarity Design

Personal skills

Multitasking

Communication

Time management

Flexibility

Attention to detail

Team player

Autonomy

Perseverance

Problem solving

Analytical thinking